(Silence; Operating Room Area)
=Stand Up for Love=
=Episode 12=
Has it really been revoked?
Would I lie to you?
We're rich.
We're about to become rich!
(Load-Side Water Separator)
The richest of the rich.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
Revoking the prenuptial agreement
is only the first step.
Next,
I'll make Lin Lulu cheat.
I'll make her the main one to blame
in this marriage.
After the divorce,
with a few more tricks,
we can take back all
of the Lin family's assets.
To make all that happen,
there's one final step.
Su Qinglan is still alive.
We still have to wait?
We've waited for two years.
A little longer won't hurt.
What's wrong?
You look troubled.
It's nothing.
I just felt that at the hospital today,
Zhang Haotian was acting strangely.
What do you mean?
It seemed like he really fell
for Zhao Ke.
A classic trick used by con men.
Don't let it get to you.
It's different.
Back when I was Jiang Lai,
even when he asked for my opinion,
he always had this
condescending attitude,
like he had all the power.
But today,
it felt like he was
begging Zhao Ke to accept his love.
You mean
Zhao Ke could become
Zhang Haotian's weakness?
I'm not sure.
But I want to take the chance.
I rejected him clearly today.
If he still comes looking for me,
then I'll know I was right.
But I think
Zhang Haotian's weakness
is money.
We have to take everything away
from him to break him.
Especially when he's worked so hard
to get something,
only to lose it all.
That's what will make him wish
he were dead.
Enough.
Jiang Lai,
you belong on the stage.
Don't let revenge blind you.
Go pursue your dreams.
But I've already...
Wait.
Please come in.
This is the person I mentioned before,
the private dance instructor, Lang Yue.
Jiang Lai.
Ms. Lang is not a stranger.
I watched your ENT competition
from two years ago.
You won first place.
It was just a small competition,
Ms. Lang.
I have a friend who was one
of the judges that night.
He said he had high hopes for the girl
named Jiang Lai.
He believed that one day,
you would win the Benesh Dance
Grand Prize.
I hope you can continue.
And I'll do everything
I can to help you.
You need to understand,
age is never kind to dancers.
Especially after losing so much time.
All right, Ms. Lang.
I just got a bottle of fine wine.
Come have a taste?
Sure.
(What's going on?)
Mom!
Mom, please open your eyes
and look at me!
Mom!
Mr. Li.
You've been watching over her here
for days.
Get some rest.
I'll look after my mother-in-law.
Someone will come to relieve me soon.
I'll leave when he gets here.
Su Qinglan's secretary has been here
the whole time.
I can't make a move.
The secretary?
Then you can use him
to get rid of Su Qinglan.
You have a way?
Mom, wake up!
Mom! Mom!
I'll listen to you from now on.
Can you please wake up?
Please wake up and look at me.
- Mom, don't leave me alone!
- Lulu.
Mom!
Making a move directly
is too risky.
I'll first figure out this
secretary's schedule.
Then find a chance to get him
to eat some mushrooms.
Can you hear me, Mom?
Mom!
Lulu.
- Lulu, don't be sad.
- Mom, wake up!
- She passed away suddenly.
- Mom!
The police have already started
investigating Mr. Li.
(Killing with a Borrowed Hand)
♪Listen, the wind chimes softly whisper♪
♪I should forget you♪
♪But I have the will,
yet not the strength♪
♪To carry on♪
♪The scenery you once longed to see♪
♪You no longer have the strength♪
♪You want me to go there for you♪
♪I look up and see a hollow sky♪
♪Your freedom♪
♪Has become my cage♪
♪My hand brushes over your smile
in the photograph♪
♪This glass of wine is filled
with sorrow♪
♪I look up at the beautiful night sky♪
♪You told me♪
♪I would shine like a star♪
♪But you forgot to teach me♪
♪How to live without you♪
♪I look up♪
♪The starry sky♪
♪So hazy and blurred♪